A mother's love is forever.
Mama is a horror film directed by Andy Muschietti.
Guillermo del Toro presents Mama, a supernatural thriller that tells the haunting tale of two
little girls who disappeared into the woods the day that their parents were killed.
When they are rescued years later and begin a new life, they find that
someone or something still wants to come tuck them in at night.
Annabel, played by Jessica Chastain.
Lucas Desange, played by Nikolaj Coster-Waldau.
Victoria Desange, played by Megan Charpentier.
Lilly Desange, played by Isabelle Nélisse.
Dr. Dreyfuss, played by Daniel Kash.
Mama (voice), played by Melina Matthews.
Mama is a 2013 English-language supernatural horror film directed and co-written by Andy
Muschietti in his directorial debut and based on his 2008 Argentine short film Mamá.
A co-production between Spain and Canada, the film stars Jessica Chastain, Nikolaj Coster-Waldau, Megan
Charpentier, Isabelle Nélisse, Daniel Kash, and Javier Botet as the title character.
The film follows two young girls abandoned in a forest cabin, fostered by an unknown entity that they fondly call "Mama",
which eventually follows them to their new suburban home led by two adults after their uncle retrieves them.
It was produced by J.
Miles Dale and co-written by Barbara Muschietti, with
Guillermo del Toro serving as executive producer.
The film was theatrically released on 18 January 2013, by Universal Pictures.
Mama received positive reviews from critics, although its story was criticized, and was a
box office success, grossing $148 million against a $15 million budget.
The film explores themes of musician, supernatural,
haunted house, feral child, car crash.
The tone is dark.